Guide to the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records, 1981-2002 UA 366
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Drawings
  - Subseries C: Architectural
    - A9
      - A9.35, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 7)
      - A9.36, Interior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 8)
      - A9.36, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 9)
      - A9.37, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 10)
      - A9.38, Interior Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 11)
      - A9.38, Interior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 12)
      - A9.38, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 13)
      - A9.39, Interior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 14)
      - A9.39, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 15)
      - A9.40, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 16)
      - A9.41, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 17)
  - Subseries D: Structural
    - Early Drafts
      - S1.01, General Notes, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 18)
      - S1.01, General Notes, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 19)
      - S1.03, General Notes, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 20)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 21)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 22)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 12/09/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 23)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 24)
      - S3.01, Column Key Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 25)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 26)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 27)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 12/09/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 28)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 29)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 30)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 31)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 12/09/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 32)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 33)
      - S3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 34)
      - S3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 35)
      - S3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 12/9/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 36)
      - S3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 37)
      - S3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 38)
      - S3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 39)
      - S3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 12/9/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 40)
      - S3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 41)
      - S3.05, Roof Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 42)
    - Later Drafts
      - S1.01, General Notes, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 1)
      - S1.02, General Notes, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 2)
      - S1.03, General Notes, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 3)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 2/23/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 4)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 5)
      - S2.01, Column Key Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 6)
      - S2.02, Column Key Plan, 2/23/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 7)
      - S2.02, Column Key Plan, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 8)
      - S2.03, Column Key Plan, 2/23/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 9)
      - S2.03, Column Key Plan, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 10)
      - S2.04, Column Key Plan, 2/23/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 11)
      - S2.04, Column Key Plan, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 12)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 2/23/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 13)
      - S3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 14)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 15)
      - S3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 16)
      - S3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 17)
      - S3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 18)
      - S3.05, Roof Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 19)
      - S4.01, Foundation Details, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 20)
      - S4.02, Foundation Typical Details, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 21)
      - S4.03, Floor 1 Details, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 22)
      - S4.04, Floor 1 Details, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 23)
      - S4.11, Concrete Framing Typical Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 24)
      - S4.12, Concrete Framing Typical Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 25)
      - S5.01, Roof Typical Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 26)
      - S5.01, Roof Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 27)
      - S5.03, Roof Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 28)
      - S5.10, Brace Frame and Details, 12/22/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 29)
      - S5.11, Truss Elevation and Details, 12/9/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 30)
      - S6.01, Column Schedule, 2/16/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 31)
      - S6.03, Beam Schedules Floor 1 & 2, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 32)
      - S6.04, Beam Schedules Floor 2, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 33)
      - S6.05, Beam Schedules Floor 3 & 4, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 34)
      - S6.11, Slab Schedules, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 35)
      - S6.21, Post-Tensioned Beams and Detail, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 178, Folder 1, Page 36)
  - Subseries E: Mechanical and Plumbing
    - M1
      - M1.01, Underfloor Plumbing Plan, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 1)
      - M1.02, Floor 1 Mechanical/Plumbing, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 2)
      - M1.02, Floor 1 Mechanical/Plumbing, 5/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 3)
      - M1.02, Floor 1 Mechanical/Plumbing, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 4)
      - M1.02, Floor 1 Mechanical/Plumbing, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 5)
      - M1.03, Floor 2 Mechanical/Plumbing, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 6)
      - M1.03, Floor 2 Mechanical/Plumbing, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 7)
      - M1.03, Floor 2 Mechanical/Plumbing, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 8)
      - M1.04, Floor 3 Mechanical/Plumbing, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 9)
      - M1.04, Floor 3 Mechanical/Plumbing, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 10)
      - M1.04, Floor 3 Mechanical/Plumbing, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 11)
      - M1.05, Floor 4 Mechanical/Plumbing, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 12)
      - M1.05, Floor 4 Mechanical/Plumbing, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 13)
      - M1.05, Floor 4 Mechanical/Plumbing, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 14)
      - M1.06, Roof Mechanical/Plumbing, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 15)
    - M2
      - M2.01, Mechanical and Plumbing Partial Plan, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 16)
      - M2.01, Mechanical and Plumbing Partial Plan, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 17)
      - M2.01, Mechanical and Plumbing Partial Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 18)
      - M2.02, Mechanical and Plumbing Partial Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 19)
    - M3
      - M3.01, Mechanical Schematics, 5/26/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 20)
      - M3.02, Mechanical Schematics, 5/26/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 21)
      - M3.02, Mechanical Schematics, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 22)
      - M3.02, Mechanical Schematics, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 23)
      - M3.03, Plumbing (Dom. Water) & Fire Protection Risers, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 24)
      - M3.04, Plumbing (Sanitary) Risers, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 25)
    - M4
      - M4.01, Mechanical and Plumbing Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 26)
      - M4.03, Mechanical and Plumbing Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 2, Page 27)
  - Subseries F: Electrical
    - E1
      - E1.00, Underfloor Electrical Plan, 1/2/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 1)
      - E1.01, Floor 1 Electrical Lighting Plan, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 2)
      - E1.01, Floor 1 Electrical Lighting Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 3)
      - E1.02, Floor 2 Electrical Lighting Plan, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 4)
      - E1.02, Floor 2 Electrical Lighting Plan, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 5)
      - E1.02, Floor 2 Electrical Lighting Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 6)
      - E1.03, Floor 3 Electrical Lighting Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 7)
      - E1.04, Floor 4 Electrical Lighting Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 8)
      - E1.05, Roof Electrical Lighting Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 9)
    - E2
      - E2.01, Floor 1 Electrical Power Plan, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 10)
      - E2.01, Floor 1 Electrical Power Plan, 5/26/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 11)
      - E2.01, Floor 1 Electrical Power Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 12)
      - E2.02, Floor 2 Electrical Power Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 13)
      - E2.03, Floor 3 Electrical Power Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 14)
      - E2.04, Floor 4 Electrical Power Plan, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 15)
      - E2.04, Floor 4 Electrical Power Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 16)
    - E3
      - E3.01, Electrical Partial Plans, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 17)
      - E3.01, Electrical Partial Plans, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 18)
      - E3.01, Electrical Partial Plans, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 19)
      - E3.02, Electrical Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 20)
    - E4
      - E4.01, Electrical Distribution Diagram, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 21)
      - E4.01, Electrical Distribution Diagram, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 22)
      - E4.01, Electrical Distribution Diagram, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 23)
      - E4.02, Electrical Distribution Diagram, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 24)
      - E4.02, Electrical Distribution Diagram, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 25)
  - Subseries F: Audiovisual
    - AV0.0, Audio Visual General Notes & Legend, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 26)
    - AV3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 27)
    - AV3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 28)
    - AV3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 29)
    - AV3.21, Floor 1 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 178, Folder 3, Page 30)
  - Magnified Drawings, n.d. (Drawer 179, Folder 2, Page 1-4)
- Duncan Hall Addendum
  - Subseries A: Photographs
    - HAKCO progress photographs, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Envelope 1-2)
    - Progress photographs, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Envelope 3-10)
  - Subseries B: Planning and construction
    - Planning and space allocation, 1988-1995 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - CEB program reports, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Campaign for Computational Engineering, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Texas Instruments proposal for funding, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bridge design estimates, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Keck Foundation proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Sun Microsystems request for funding, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Selling Chain request for funding, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Planters iconography (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Audio/visual equipment, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Furniture (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Descriptions of building (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Rice cornerstones and signs (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Studies brochure (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Building publicity, 1993-2001 (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
    - Photographs (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Groundbreaking, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - CEB construction (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Dedication and reception, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Keith Cooper design notes, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Keith Cooper correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Keith Cooper. Outram's building: Icons, themes and images, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C: John Outram Associates
    - John Outram Associates. Short History of the Robot Order, 1973-1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - John Outram Associates. Selected projects, 1981-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - John Outram Associates. Review of Judge Institute, Cambridge, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - John Outram Associates. Spaces for social interaction and the exchange of ideas, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - John Outram Associates. Planning, correspondence, drawings, renderings, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - John Outram Associates. CEB elevations, interiors, floor plans (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - John Outram Associates. Draft interiors, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - John Outram Associates. CEB elevations, site plan, floor plans (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - John Outram Associates. Report to the Rice University Selection Board, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - John Outram Associates. CEB design report:Schematic design, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - John Outram Associates. Memo concerning structural engineering, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - John Outram Associates. Progress report: decorative systems, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - John Outram Associates. Schematic design stage, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - John Outram Associates. Short report on brickwork, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - John Outram Associates. CEB interior colors, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - John Outram Associates. The CEB, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - John Outram Associates. A critical view of theory, Pumping iron, CEB dedication, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - John Outram. Science and the column, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - John Outram Associates. CEB Rice, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - John Outram Associates. The CEB: Outline of an iconography, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - John Outram. Thoughts on the exterior spaces: CEB southern courtyard, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - John Outram. The log of the navigator, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - John Outram. The architecture of time, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - John Outram. As others see us: Thoughts addressed to an intending critic, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - John Outram. Iconography, colors (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - John Outram. Doodles (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - John Outram Associates. Appendix to question 1 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - John Outram. Interview, Wired Magazine (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Subseries D: Audio/video
    - C. Sidney Burrus. Computational engineering. VHS and audio tapes, 1994 (Box 22, Envelope 33)
    - Building talk, Computational Engineering Window Dub, VHS tapes, 1995 (Box 22, Envelope 34)
  - Subseries E: Donor signage and color details
    - Donor signage and color details, printed on 11x17 paper (Box 23)